treylink.com 2017-06-03

# Privacy Policy - Buildbox | Game Maker | Video Game Software

(V1.01 – Effective February 18th, 2016)

**PLEASE READ THE FOLLOWING CAREFULLY. YOUR USE OF THIS WEBSITE IS SUBJECT TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS.**

**Index**

  1. **Notice**
  2. **Personally Identifiable Information That We Collect**
  3. **E-mail Newsletter Subscriptions**
  4. **User Accounts**
  5. **Special Promotions and Purchases; Submission of Content to be Published**
  6. **Information Collected by Other Means or Media**
  7. **Information About Other People**
  8. **Customer Service**
  9. **Non-Personally Identifiable Information That We Collect**
  10. **Cookies and Related Technology**
  11. **Not Intended for Persons Under 18**
  12. **Use, Disclosure, and Sharing of Information**
    1. Non-Personally Identifiable Information
    2. Personally Identifiable Information
    3. Information Disclosed to other Users of this Website
  13. **Our Commitment to Data Security**
  14. **Hyperlinks To and From Other Sites**
  15. **Consent to Processing in the United States**
  16. **Contact Us Regarding Privacy**
  17. **Notification of Changes**

* * *

**I. Notices**

The “Website” refers to all of the websites at www.buildbox.com, and any of it/their subdomains, or a successor website as indicated by COMPANY. This Website is owned or operated by 8cell, Inc., or any successor to ownership of the Website, and/or its subsidiary companies in the United States of America (collectively the “COMPANY”). This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) applies to information that You provide to COMPANY or is collected about You via this Website and/or by Your use of services (collectively, “Services”) that may be provided by this Website or by the COMPANY via some other means, including as set forth below and as defined in the applicable Terms and Conditions or other terms.

This Privacy Policy is intended to provide You notice of COMPANY’s information management practices, including the types of information gathered, how it is used and safeguarded, and the degree to which You may control the maintenance and sharing of Your information. Your use of any COMPANY Service or Website constitutes acceptance of and agreed to this Privacy Policy and any other applicable terms. This Privacy Policy is part of and incorporated by reference into COMPANY’S Terms and Conditions.

**II. Personally Identifiable Information That We Collect**

“Users” refer to users of the Websites and Services. Because the Websites and Services are intended to facilitate marketing and transactions among its Users, personally identifiable information that You provide or is provided about You, such as but not limited to Your name, company name, shipping address, billing address, telephone numbers, e-mail address, and payment information such as billing terms may be shared with other Users. Information such credit card information is only shared with parties associated with You or as needed to facilitate a transaction You have agreed to.

Please be aware that COMPANY has a right to indicate to the public what Brand Users and Buyers have accounts with or otherwise uses the Website and/or Services.

**III. E-mail Newsletter Subscriptions**

When You create a User Account or accept one, download materials from the Company, or purchase the products or Services of the Company, You are agreeing to be subscribed to our e-mail newsletters, if any. You may also be asked for other information at the same or later time.

**IV. User Accounts**

In order to use some of our Services, You will need to register and create, or otherwise accept, a user account (“User Account”). Note that when You log into a User Account, You are agreeing to be bound by this Privacy Policy and the Terms and Conditions, and are also “accepting” Your User Account. There may or may not be a cost to create a User Account. You may be asked to choose a user name, screen name, or member name (each, a “User Name”) and password. You may also be asked to provide certain personally identifiable information and other information about Yourself, such as Your first and last name, company name, billing and shipping address, telephone number, and e-mail address. The Website allows You to update certain information when You are logging in.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to any information You may disclose publicly in such Services. In some instances, You may choose to create a “Public Profile” that will be available to others on the Internet. Public Profiles are managed entirely by You, and You are solely responsible for Your Public Profile’s content and its “public” or “private” status. COMPANY bears no responsibility for any action or policies of any third parties who collect any information that users may disclose in user forums or other public areas of this Website. You are also responsible for maintaining and updating the registration information in Your User Account with current and complete information.

You can unsubscribe from receiving marketing e-mails from the Website by clicking the link contained within such e-mails sent to You. You cannot unsubscribe from receiving correspondence regarding non-marketing e-mails, including but not limited to correspondence with parties involved in a transaction with You, or emails with COMPANY regarding Your User Account and activities on or through the Website.

You should be aware that it is not always possible to completely remove or modify information in our databases. In addition, we may institute a policy in which User information is deleted after a certain amount of time, and therefore, Your User information may no longer exist in COMPANY’s active database(s). Even if You choose to unsubscribe or otherwise modify Your User Account settings, COMPANY reserves the right to contact You regarding Your account and Your use of this Website and/or the Services.

**V. Special Promotions and Purchases; Submission of Content to be Published**

To participate in some Services such as sweepstakes, contests and surveys (“Special Promotions”), or to make online purchases or subscriptions (such purchases or subscriptions herein referred to as “Purchases”), You may need to provide personally identifiable information, such as name, address, e-mail address, phone number, and date of birth. Your information may be collected by COMPANY or by a third party, such as a co-sponsor or a vendor involved in, or providing services in connection with, a Special Promotion, or an e-commerce partner in the case of a Purchase.

If You make a Purchase or enter a sweepstakes or other Special Promotion on one of our sites or through our Services, COMPANY will collect Your personally identifiable information, and You are deemed to consent to us providing Your information to third parties who provide certain services such as processing of credit card transactions, customer service, promotion or sweepstakes administration, order fulfillment and/or prize delivery, as applicable. (As more fully described below in Section XII, these third parties are generally prohibited from using this information for their own marketing purposes and/or from sharing, selling, or otherwise distributing any personal data of our customers, unless You choose to opt in for such additional uses and/or disclosure by the third parties, under their respective privacy policies.). Also, by entering a sweepstakes or other Special Promotion, You are agreeing to the official rules that govern that sweepstakes or other Special Promotion, which may contain specific provisions applicable to You, including, except where prohibited by law, allowing the sponsor(s) of the promotion to use Your name, voice or likeness in advertising or marketing associated with the promotion.

If You make a purchase or enter a promotion (such as a sweepstakes) in which COMPANY is participating on a third party’s website (or through some other means or medium), we will collect Your information from the third party only if You opt-in to receive additional communications from us, or we are required to fulfill some function in relation to Your activity (e.g., to send Your order or deliver a prize).

If You submit to the Website a comment, photograph or other content to be published, online or offline (including on-air, in a DVD, or any other format), we may publish Your name or other personally identifiable information in connection with publishing the content and You are hereby deemed to give us permission to do such.

**VI. Information Collected by Other Means or Media**

In some situations, we may also collect personally identifiable information and other information about You through other means, directly or indirectly. For example, if You access any COMPANY content, or purchase such content via Your wireless carrier or through another third party, COMPANY may collect information directly from You or through the third party. Likewise, if You use our software, or provide information to other companies who share information about their customers, we may collect additional information about You. In each of these cases, COMPANY will apply this Privacy Policy to any personally identifiable information.

**VII. Information About Other People**

Some COMPANY Websites and Services may ask You to submit personally identifiable, as well as other information about other people and/or their affiliated companies.

Such information may be used to facilitate transactions among Users, COMPANY, and third parties. As such, such information may be shared and used by all such parties to the extent COMPANY desires or otherwise allows such information to be shared. You are hereby accepting and agreeing to such use and sharing of information.

**VIII. Customer Service**

Some Services may offer support and technical assistance through customer service centers via telephone, online chat, or e-mail. Whenever You communicate with customer service, You do so with the understanding that an operator may view and make changes to the information in Your User Account in order to provide the assistance that You need.

**IX. Non-Personally Identifiable Information That We Collect**

As part of the registration process for some Services, You may be asked to provide information that does not personally identify You. For example, You may be asked to provide information concerning Your personal preferences, purchasing habits, and the like. This information is generally optional but may be included in Your User Account profile. COMPANY requests this information to understand You better and to also bring to Your attention new services, programs, or offers that may be of interest to You.

In many cases, COMPANY will automatically collect certain non-personally identifiable information about Your use of the Websites and Services. COMPANY might collect, among other things, information concerning the type of Internet browser or computer operating system You are using, the domain name of Your Internet service provider, Your “click path” through COMPANY sites or “click-through” from an e-mail, the Website or advertisement that was linked to or from COMPANY site when You visited, and Your IP address. To do this, COMPANY may use cookies and other technology (see below). If You are using any Services of ours that are wireless, we may also automatically collect information such as the type of wireless device You are using, Your mobile identification number (assigned by Your telecommunications carrier) and telecommunications carrier. Your use of our Websites and Services, and information provided through these technologies, will be anonymous unless You provide us with personally identifiable information, have provided such information in the past, or have a User Account.

**X. Cookies and Related Technology**

This Website’s pages or e-mail messages may contain cookies, web beacons (also known as clear gifs), or similar technologies as they become available. Cookies are information files that this Website may place on Your computer to provide extended functionality. COMPANY may use cookies for a number of purposes, such as tracking usage patterns on the Website, measuring the effectiveness of advertising, limiting multiple responses and registrations, facilitating Your ability to navigate the Website, providing advertising to You about our products and services or those of third parties on the Website or other websites, and/or as part of a verification or screening process. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. Most browsers will allow you to erase cookies from Your computer hard drive, block acceptance of cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. You should refer to Your browser instructions, “Help” screen, or similar such resource to learn more about how to manage cookies and possibly reset Your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent by indicating this in the preferences, options, or similar such menu in Your browser. However, it is possible that some parts of this Website will not operate correctly if You disable cookies and You may not be able to take advantage of some of this Website’s features. You should consult with Your browser’s provider/manufacturer if You have any questions regarding disabling cookies.

COMPANY’s web pages may include advertisements for third parties and their products, and those third-party advertisements may include a cookie or web beacon served by the third party. COMPANY does not control cookies in such third party ads, and visitors are encouraged to check the privacy policies of advertisers and/or ad services to learn about their use of cookies and other technology. COMPANY’s Privacy Policy does not cover the use of information collected from You by third party ad servers. These companies may use information (not including Your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number) about Your visits to this and other Websites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to You.

A web beacon is a small graphic image that allows the party that set the web beacon to monitor and collect certain information about the viewer of the web page, web-based document or e-mail message, such as the type of browser requesting the web beacon, the IP address of the computer that the web beacon is sent to and the time the web beacon was viewed. Web beacons can be very small and invisible to the user, but, in general, any electronic image viewed as part of a web page or e-mail, including HTML based content, can act as a web beacon. COMPANY may use web beacons to count visitors to the web pages on the Website or to monitor how our users navigate the Website, and COMPANY may include web beacons in e-mail messages in order to count how many messages sent were actually opened, acted upon or forwarded.

**XI. Not Intended for Persons Under 18**

COMPANY recognizes the sensitivity of personally identifiable information concerning children and minors. COMPANY is committed to complying with all applicable laws and regulations regarding children, including the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”). This site is only intended for persons 18 and over. If You are under 18 years of age, immediately discontinue use of this site and leave this Website. COMPANY will not knowingly collect, maintain, or disclose any personally identifiable information from a person under 18.

If you are a parent or guardian who has discovered that Your child under the age of 18 has submitted his or her personally identifiable information without Your permission or consent, COMPANY will make reasonable efforts to remove the information from its active list, at Your request. To request the removal of Your child’s information, please send an e-mail to [support@buildbox.com](mailto:support@buildbox.com) and be sure to include in Your message the same User Name and password and/or e-mail address that Your child submitted.

**XII. Use, Disclosure, and Sharing of Information**

**a. Non-Personally Identifiable Information**

From time to time, COMPANY may use and share with third parties aggregate, non-personally identifiable User information to show general demographic and preference information among users of COMPANY Websites. For example, COMPANY may produce and share with others “trend reports” using such aggregate, non-personally identifiable User information, generated based on information gathered on Users from order information (i.e. products purchased, amount spent, type of product, general addresses to be shipped to etc), retailer information related to purchases (i.e. type of retailer and their buying habits) and brand information (i.e. type of product a Brand showcases).

When You visit or download information from this Website, our web servers may automatically collect website usage information. Website usage information is non-personally identifying information that describes how our visitors use the Website. It can include the number and frequency of visitors to each web page and the length of their stays, browser type, referrer data that identifies the web page visited prior and subsequent to visiting the Website, and IP addresses (see below for more information on IP addresses). COMPANY may use IP addresses for a number of purposes, such as system administration, to generally determine Your computer’s server location, to report aggregate information to our business partners or to audit use of the Website. We also may determine Your screen resolution and the technology available in order to serve You the most appropriate version of a web page, e-mail or similar service.

**b. Personally Identifiable Information**

COMPANY uses information about You to deliver the Services that You request, to keep You informed about changes affecting our Services or Your account, to inform You of other Services or offers in which You might be interested, and to improve and enhance our sites and Services. If You provide COMPANY with personally identifiable information, we will take all reasonable and appropriate steps to protect it from unauthorized disclosure.

When You create a User Account or accept one, You are opting in to receive e-mail from us. You can always opt out of future marketing messages by following the directions in each message to “unsubscribe”. However, if You choose to opt out of marketing messages, we reserve the right to contact You regarding Your account status, technical support, product information, changes to account terms, and any other matter that might affect our service to You and/or any products You purchased from us or registered with us, as applicable.

As stated in the Terms and Conditions, You will be deemed to have consented to the disclosure to, and use by, a subsequent owner or operator of a COMPANY Website or Service, of any information about You contained in the applicable COMPANY database, if COMPANY or one of its companies assigns its rights and obligations regarding any of Your information at the time of a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or substantially all of COMPANY’s or such COMPANY company’s assets related to the applicable site or Service to a subsequent owner or operator. In the event of such a merger, acquisition, or sale, Your continued use of the Website or any related Service signifies Your agreement to be bound by the Terms and Conditions and Privacy Policy of the Website’s or Service’s subsequent owner or operator.

COMPANY and other entities may work together in order to provide portions of COMPANY Websites and some Services (e.g., to fulfill prizes won in a sweepstakes, or to provide other support for a Service). These companies will handle Your personally identifiable information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

As stated above in Section V, COMPANY may also work with third parties to provide some Services on our Websites. In connection with those Services, You are deemed to consent to us sharing Your information with third parties who provide services such as processing of credit card transactions, customer service, promotion administration, order fulfillment and/or prize delivery, as applicable. Third parties who provide, or participate in, Services on COMPANY Websites are prohibited from using our customers’ personally identifiable information for marketing purposes and/or from sharing, selling, or otherwise using such information, unless You choose to opt in to marketing, sharing, or other uses by the third parties. If You do not want Your information to be used for marketing (or other purposes unrelated to the provision of COMPANY Services) by a third party who participates in a Service on one of our sites, do not opt in to such use by that third party when You register to participate in the Service.  
Please note that whenever You opt in to receive future communications from a third party, Your information will be subject to the third party’s privacy policy. If You later decide that You do not want that third party to use Your information, You will need to contact the third party directly, as we have no control over how third parties use information. You should always review the privacy policy of any party that collects Your information to determine how that entity will handle Your information.

COMPANY will not share, sell, rent, or disclose any personally identifiable information that we have collected except as stated herein, or in the following instances: 1) we have been given Your consent to disclose; 2) we have previously informed You of the disclosure, including by means of our Privacy Policy or on the Website, or through the Service where You provided Your information; 3) we are required by law, legal process, or court order to disclose; 4) disclosure is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may cause or be causing harm to, or interference with, COMPANY’s rights or property, other COMPANY Website users, or anyone else; or 5) to respond to an inquiry, request or complaint that You have made. COMPANY may also use IP addresses in cooperation with Internet service providers to identify users if we deem it necessary to comply with law, to enforce compliance with this Privacy Policy or our Terms and Conditions, or to protect our sites, customers, or others.

**c. Information Disclosed to other Users of this Website**

The Services of the Website include functionality that may allow You i) to market or advertise Your services or items You wish to sell (such as clothing and other fashion related items), ii) view information about or contact others about the services or items they wish to sell, and/or iii) transact with others. When You seek to market or advertise the services or items You wish to sell, You are consenting that information related to such services or items, as well as Your identity and contact information, will be shared publicly with other users of the Website. When You seek to contact others about the services or items they wish to sell, You are consenting that information about You, such as Your interests, preferences, identity and contact information, will be shared with those You are seeking to contact. When You seek to transact with others, Your communication will be shared with those You are seeking to transaction with, as well as Your identity and contact information.

Some COMPANY Websites and Services may ask You to submit personally identifiable information, as well as other information about other people and/or their affiliated companies. Such information may be used to facilitate transactions among Users, COMPANY, and third parties. As such, such information may be shared and used by all such parties. You are hereby accepting and agreeing to such use and sharing of information.

Some of the ways that such information of Users and other third parties may be shared and used are as follows:

  1. Users may be able to view all information of or regarding each other.

**XIII. Our Commitment to Data Security**

While COMPANY takes reasonable and appropriate precautions to protect Your personally identifiable information from unauthorized disclosure and to prevent possible security breaches in our Websites, Services, and customer databases, no website, Internet transmission, computer system, or wireless connection is completely secure. Consequently, COMPANY cannot guarantee that unauthorized access, hacking, data loss, or other breaches will never occur. Your use of COMPANY Websites and Services is at Your own risk. COMPANY urges You to take steps to determine what information You will submit to the Website, keep Your information safe by memorizing Your password or keeping it in a safe place (separate from Your account information), logging out of Your User Account, and closing Your Web browser.

Whenever You give COMPANY sensitive or confidential information (for example, credit card numbers for Purchases), COMPANY will take commercially reasonable steps to protect the transmission of such information by establishing a secure connection with Your Web browser. COMPANY employs a security technology known as a secure-socket-layer (“SSL”) to protect the transmission of payment information to the site. Unless otherwise specified herein or on the Website where You make a Purchase, credit and debit card numbers are used only for payment processing and are not retained for marketing purposes.

**XIV. Hyperlinks To and From Other Sites**

COMPANY sites may frame, and/or contain links to, or advertisements about, non-COMPANY Web sites. Other sites may also reference, advertise, or link to COMPANY Websites. COMPANY does not endorse or sponsor other websites, is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of non-COMPANY sites, expressly disclaims any statements or assertions made on such websites, and denies and disclaims all liability associated with Your use of, and the content on, such other sites and advertisements.

**XV. Consent to Processing in the United States**

By providing any personally identifiable information to COMPANY, all users, including, without limitation, users in the member states of the European Union, fully understand and unambiguously consent to this Privacy Policy and to the collection, storage, and processing of such information in the United States of America.

**XVI. Contact Us Regarding Privacy**

COMPANY is dedicated to protecting Your personally identifiable information and welcomes comments and questions on this Privacy Policy. You may e-mail Your questions or comments to:  
[support@buildbox.com](mailto:support@buildbox.com).

Please note that information submitted to the Website via a “contact us,” “help” or other similar e-mail address or form will not necessarily receive a response. We will not use the information provided to these e-mail addresses or forms for marketing purposes unrelated to Your request.

**XVII. Notification of Changes**

COMPANY reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy and its Terms and Conditions at any time. In case of any material change to the Privacy Policy, we will replace the “Privacy Policy” link on the home page of our sites with a link entitled “Updated Privacy Policy” for no less than 30 days. All changes to the Privacy Policy will be effective when posted, and Your continued use of any COMPANY Website or Service after the posting will constitute acceptance of, and agreement to be bound by, those changes.

**8Cell, Inc.**  
Last updated: February 18th, 2016  
Copyright  2014 © 8Cell, Inc.  
ALL RIGHTS RESERVED
